http://nfaonline.org/privacy-policy

Effective October 23, 2006
Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the NFA Web site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information Please note: Credit card information is collected through, but does not remain on, the Web site. Once an order is processed, it is not saved.On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:Name Address Phone NumberThe Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Our Commitment To Children’s PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.How You Can Access Or Correct Your InformationYou can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to the site under the Member Access section. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
Community
NFA News & Updates
Community Board
Jobs & Internships
Instrument Notices
The NFA Blog
Community Blog
Submit a Blog Post
